Contact

barbrn1002@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/barbara-wickham-17975378 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

ACLS

Nursing

Languages

English

Certifications

CCRN, ACLS, BLS certified. I also teach ACLS and BLS

Barbara Wickham

RN, MSN, ANP-BC, CCRN Mansfield, Ohio

Summary

Currently employed as a Nurse Practitioner with Avita Health
System as an Occupational Medicine Nurse Practitioner. Previously

employed as an NP with HCI Hospitalists, Inc. at Ohio Health, Med Central Mansfield Hospital (2012-2015).

Strong background in Critical Care Medicine, having 18 years experience in various ICU settings.

ACLS/BLS certified. Certified ACLS/BLS instructor.

Experience

Nurse Practitioner at Avita Health System Occupational Medicine April 2015 - Present (5 years 3 months)

I work at ArcelorMittal in Shelby Ohio, and the Avita WorkWell Clinic in Bucyrus, Ohio as an occupational health nurse practitioner.

HCI Care Services
Nurse Practitioner
December 2012 - June 2015 (2 years 7 months)
Med Central Health System, Mansfield, Ohio

NP with the Hospitalist group.

Samaritan Regional Health System Staff RN

April 2003 - August 2013 (10 years 5 months)

Ashland, Ohio

ICU

Education

University of Cincinnati

Masters Degree, Adult Nurse Practitioner · (2010 - 2012)

The Ohio State University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2006 - 2008)